## Tony Schwebach

Tony.Schwebach.developer@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tonyschwebach/ https://github.com/tonyschwebach

#### JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Junior software engineer leveraging corporate accounting and finance experience to build better business tools. MERN stack stills gained from the Georgia Institute of Technology Coding Bootcamp. Recognized as employee of the quarter for collaborative leadership, problem solving, and analytical work and to automate processes enabling significant growth with limited additional resources.

HTML5

React.is

Express.js

CSS3 & Bootstrap JavaScript & jQuery

Node.js

MongoDB

MySQL

APIs & AJAX

Python

Git & Terminal

**Agile Methods** 

#### PROGRAMMING PROJECTS

#### JavaScript Quiz Game - Repo: https://github.com/tonyschwebach/javascript-quiz-game

2020

Trivia game which quizzes users' knowledge of basic JavaScript concepts.

Tools: JavaScript, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS

#### Weather Dashboard – Repo: https://github.com/tonyschwebach/weather-dashboard

2020

Provides current weather and 5-day forecast for user specified locations.

Tools: AJAX, JavaScript, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS

## Digital Coffee Landing Page - Repo: https://github.com/ahnlok/digital-coffee

2020

- Inspiring users with positive quotes and a clean UI/UX upon opening their browser.
- Tools:JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Bootstrap, HTML5, Git

#### Financial Statements SQL Power Pivot – propriety of Krystal Restaurants LLC

2020

- Created real-time, accurate financial statements with drill down capability from the ERP database.
- Tools: SQL, MS Access, MS Dynamics GP, MS Excel

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Krystal Restaurants LLC - Atlanta, GA

## **Accounting Manager**

Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

Supervised 2 direct reports responsible for general ledger, accounts receivable, and fixed assets.

Built Excel model adding insights on payroll expenses for 180 corporate locations.

## UniPro Foodservice Inc - Atlanta, GA

## **Accounting Director**

Oct 2018 - Aug 2020

Managed team of 16 staff responsible for all operational accounting and treasury activities of \$1 Billion company.

- Built workflow KPI dashboards using SQL to identify billing delays and improve daily cash flow by \$1,300,000.
- Used Visual Basic (VBA) to create KPIs in Excel and reduce past due accounts by 2.5%, equating to \$875,000.

**Billing Manager** Jul 2015 - Oct 2018

Led 4-6 direct reports responsible for invoicing and sales analysis of \$1 Billion of products and services.

- Designed digital workflow using OnBase to reduce document processing time by 30% saving \$60,000 annually.
- Automated invoicing for 20% of orders using EDI 880 invoices allowing 250% growth without additional staff.

# Tony Schwebach

Tony.Schwebach.developer@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tonyschwebach/ https://github.com/tonyschwebach

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

## UniPro Foodservice Inc – Atlanta, GA

## **General Ledger Accountant**

Jan 2015 - Jul 2015

Staff Accountant responsible for analysis, financial reporting, journal entries, and reconciliations.

- Collaborated with AS400 programmers to whiteboard, test, and deploy account reconciliation program.
- Automated banking transactions improving daily cash flow by \$100,000 and eliminating reconciliation issues.

## **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATION**

Coding Certificate, Georgia Institute of Technology – Atlanta, GA	Mar 2020
Certified Management Accountant (cert# 61150), Institute of Management Accountants	Jul 2018
Master of Business Administration, Southwest Minnesota State University – Marshall, MN	Dec 2014
Bachelor of Science (Finance & Management), Southwest Minnesota State University – Marshall, MN	Dec 2012